export default data = [
  {
      question: "Chinese is a language with many _______ differences. People living in different areas often speak different dialects.",
      options: ["sociable","legendary","regional","superior"],
      correct_option: "regional"
  },
  {
      question: "A menu serves to _____ customers about the varieties and prices of the dishes offered by the restaurant.",
      options: ["appeal","convey","inform","demand"],
      correct_option: "inform"
  },
  {
      question: "Mary and Jane often fight over which radio station to listen to. Their _______ arises mainly from their different tastes in music.",
      options: ["venture","consent","dispute","temptation"],
      correct_option: "dispute"
  },
  {
      question: "The baby polar bear is being _____ studied by the scientists. Every move he makes is carefully observed and documented.",
      options: ["prosperously","intensively","honorably","originally"],
      correct_option: "intensively"
  },
  {
      question: "At twelve, Catherine has won several first prizes in international art competitions. Her talent and skills are _____ for her age.",
      options: ["comparable","exceptional","indifferent","unconvincing"],
      correct_option: "exceptional"
  },
  {
      question: "After his superb performance, the musician received a big round of _____ from the appreciative audience.",
      options: ["vacuum","overflow","applause","spotlight"],
      correct_option: "applause"
  },
  {
      question: "The water company inspects the pipelines and _____ the water supply regularly to ensure the safety of our drinking water.",
      options: ["exhibits","monitors","interprets","converts"],
      correct_option: "monitors"
  },
  {
      question: "This year’s East Asia Summit meetings will focus on critical _____ such as energy conservation, food shortages, and global warming.",
      options: ["issues","remarks","conducts","faculties"],
      correct_option: "issues"
  },
  {
      question: "Having fully recognized Mei-ling’s academic ability, Mr. Lin strongly _____ her for admission to the university.",
      options: ["assured","promoted","estimated","recommended"],
      correct_option: "recommended"
  },
  {
      question: "The weatherman has warned about drastic temperature change in the next few days, and suggested that we check the weather on a daily basis and dress _____.",
      options: ["necessarily","significantly","specifically","accordingly"],
      correct_option: "accordingly"
  },
]